quicktransportsolutions.com 2019-03-05

# Quick Transport Solutions Inc. Privacy Policy

### [QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [info@QuickTSI.com](mailto:info@quicktsi.com) .

At [www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [https://www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, [https://www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

[https://www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Commission Junction.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [https://www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[https://www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) and [QuickTSI.com's](https://www.quicktransportsolutions.com/) privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

### QuickTSI Load Board Privacy Policy

 **1\. COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY**

This notice describes our Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy is designed to advise you about how we collect, use, and protect the personal information you provide. By visiting this Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTED.**

a) **INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US.**   
We collect any information you enter on our Site, or that you give us in any other way. This may include e-mail address, user name, password, home or other physical address, name and telephone number. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you may not be able to take advantage of our services and features. 

b) **AUTOMATIC INFORMATION.**   
When you visit a website, you disclose certain information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and the time of your visit. This Site, like many other sites, records the basic information about visits to our Site. 

**3\. USE OF INFORMATION**

The information we collect is used for administering our business activities. Occasionally we may use the information to notify you via email and/or fax about changes to our website, new services, special offers or information from companies on their behalf that offer services that we feel could help your business. 

**4\. PROTECTION OF INFORMATION**

The privacy and protection of your information is important to us. We do not make any personal information available to third parties without your permission. Your access to some services and content is password protected. You should not disclose your password to anyone. 

We use security software to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. In addition our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information. Our business practices limit employee access to confidential information and limited use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons. 

**5\. ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The information about our users is important to us. We will not disclose any individually identifiable information to any third party without first receiving that user's permission. You can review and request changes to personally identifiable information by [https://www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](http://www.quicktsi.com/) (QuickTSI Load Board).

Information that is collected that is deemed to be confidential (credit card numbers and associated card data, social security numbers, tax identification numbers) will also be collected using secure socket layer (SSL) protocol, which encrypts data sent from your browser to our servers. This data is then also encrypted in our databases, and only accessible by authorized staff within the [https://www.QuickTransportSolutions.com](https://www.quicktsi.com/) (QuickTSI Load Board) organization. 

**6\. CHILDREN**

This Site does not provide services or sell products to anyone under the age of 21. 

**7\. CONSENT**

By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**8\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

If our Privacy Policy or procedures change, we will immediately post those changes to our Site. Any changes will be effective immediately upon being posted, unless otherwise stated in the change.

**9\. EFFECTIVE DATE**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 05-May-2011.
